tech.com.pk 2019-07-14

# Privacy Policy – TechWafer

This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by  **TechWafer  **(previously The Tech)

### Personally Provided Information

You do not have to give us personal information to visit **TechWafer.com.**  If you choose to provide us with additional information through an e-mail message, inquiry form, comments, etc., we will only maintain the information as long as needed to respond to your question, inquiry, or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not give, share, sell or transfer any personal information to a third party.

### Website Traffic Analysis Software

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. We also monitor our traffic to analyze visitors information, such as, but not limited to, operating system, browsers, screen resolutions and similar.

In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.

### E-mail Newsletter

If users wish to subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, we ask for contact information. Our Daily Newsletter is powered by MailChimp, Recipients of our newsletters can unsubscribe using the instructions listed at the end of the e-mail newsletter.

### Third Party Advertising Partners

All users of techwafer.com must keep this in mind that third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browsers, or using web beacons to collect information as a result of ad serving on.

For, instance one of our partners, Google uses the [DoubleClick DART cookie](https://www.doubleclickbygoogle.com/) on  **TechWafer.com**  displaying AdSense for content ads. Similarly, other advertising partners may use their respective cookies to track advertising stats.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our SitThe non-personalnal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

#### Compliance with children’s online privacy protection act

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

#### External Links

Our websites contain links to other sites.  **TechWafer.com**  is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each website to which we may link that may collect personal information.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

The **TechWafer**  has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

#### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

#### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at  **contact@techwafer.com**

This page can be updated without any notice so please keep visiting this. This page was last updated on 24-Sept-2018.
